one of the greatest things i ever did for my life was oh by the way there's vegetables on my pants
one of the greatest things i ever did for my life was really lean into learning about myself which
then let people go out of my life that could not align with my values the bottom line for my values
is truth that's it my religion is truth so any adherence or willingness to accept colonialist
ideologies any flimsiness at addressing injustice any willful ignorance i'm out we live in a society
built of lies so when you are an adherent to truth you have to have people around you who are also
that way in order to live in purpose to dispel the lies that are keeping us enslaved and what it does
is it hones and it refines your values when you are with those who share those values you know like
iron sharpens iron you know that term so you know it's not to say that i didn't have like friends
and homies who were into you know the frivolous pop culture of it all etc but there were also people
that just kind of had to go away because they could not elevate to where i was elevating to i had
a friend say to me that she couldn't go to new orleans because they do devil worship there i knew
the minute she said that that our friendship was was never not going to be able to sustain anymore
but then on the other hand i have homies who at one point we were more so just like in the mix
of each other's lives because of our careers but then over time what has kept us in the mix of each
other's lives is that our perspectives have continued to grow and expand we have continued
to gain knowledge we have continued to actually challenge ourselves so that to me is the biggest
determinant of how you have a circle that continues to grow with you and also that is going to continue
to grow you do they constantly self-assess are they constantly challenging themselves to learn
something that may be uncomfortable it has been scientifically proven that minds that are
constantly operating in that way that have a consciousness about their consciousness are more
fortified and thus less susceptible to being brainwashed and manipulated if that ain't your circle
you got a trash circle and i'm not talking compost i've got vegetables he began to support the labor
unions uh he questioned government allocation of resources he advocated for reparations where are we
cutting the check it was after all of this when he had evolved into martin luther the king
that this nation thought to be rid of him
you